nycairporter.com 2018-11-22

# NYC Airporter Privacy Policy - We are Committed to Protecting Your Privacy

You can always visit our site without revealing who you are or providing any Personal Information. When you visit our site or visit our site through one of our partner’s sites, we do collect usage information (“session data”), but it is anonymous and is not linked to you as an individual. We use session data to better understand things like how our site is navigated, how many visitors arrive at specific pages, the length and frequency of stays at our site, the variety of searches of our site’s database, the types of browsers and computer operating systems used by our visitors and the Internet Protocol addresses from which our visitors connect to our site. We use this information to improve our site content and ease of use.

## Use of Internet Protocol (“IP”) Addresses

An IP address is a unique number that is automatically assigned to your computer whenever you’re surfing the Internet so that your computer can be identified by the main computers, known as “Web servers”, that “serve up” Web pages.

NYCAirporter.com and/or its affiliates collect IP addresses for the purposes of system administration, to report aggregated information to our advertisers, and to audit the use of our site. When Users request pages from NYCAirporter.com and/or its affiliates’ sites, our servers log the Users’ IP addresses. We do not normally link IP addresses to anything personally identifiable, which means that a User’s session will be logged, but the User will remain anonymous to us. We can and will use IP addresses to identify a User when we feel it is necessary to enforce compliance with our site terms of use or terms of service or to protect our service, site, Users or others.

## Personal Information

If you decide to register with us, we will collect Personal Information about you that you voluntarily share. We collect Personal Information that is necessary for us to provide you with the services offered on our site. As mentioned, this Personal Information includes things like your name, e-mail and mailing address and telephone number. You will provide an e-mail address and select a username and password that will be required to gain access to portions of our site.

## E-mail notifications

We may use your e-mail address or telephone number to contact you about changes to your purchased travel itinerary. To make these e-mails more useful to you, we may attach a Web beacon that provides confirmation when you open an e-mail from NYCAirporter.com. This only occurs if your computer supports such technology.

## Responses to your questions or suggestions

We will use your e-mail address or telephone number to respond when you submit a question or suggestion, or request assistance with viewing your itinerary, logging on to NYCAirporter.com, or accessing your account.

## Our Obligations

NYCAirporter.com may be required by law to disclose information you have provided in obtaining our travel services.

## Purchase Travel

Each time you purchase Bus tickets through NYCAirporter.com, you will receive confirmation of your purchase via e-mail.

## Additional Products and Services

We may partner with other companies to offer you additional products or services. If you sign up for any of these additional products or services, we will share your name and any other Personal Information that is necessary for these other companies to provide the products or services you have signed up for. This policy will not cover the use of your Personal Information by these other companies. We encourage you to read each other company’s privacy policy before signing up for any of its products or services.

## Notification of Changes

We may change this policy from time to time. If we decide to change this policy in a material way (for example, a change regarding disclosure of Personal Information), we will post notice of the change on our site and notify you via e-mail at the address you have provided to us or pop-up screen at least thirty (30) days before putting the change into effect. If we decide to change our policy in a less significant way, we will simply post notice of the change on our site at least thirty (30) days before putting the change into effect. If any proposed change is unacceptable to you, you may request that we remove your Personal Information from our records.

## How We Protect Your Information

We are committed to safeguarding your information. For that reason we employ a staff of security technology professionals and utilize a full range of the best security technology available. Specifically, your information is secured from unauthorized access from the Internet through market leading firewall technology. We also protect the connection between your computer and our server from eavesdropping through industry-standard encryption technology known as Secure Socket Layer (SSL). Depending on your browser, this SSL will have encryption keys of up to 64 bits. To ensure that we fulfill our commitment to safeguard your information, we continually assess new technology for protecting your information to make sure that our information handling practices are in accordance with the highest industry standards and best practices on the Internet at all times.

## Links

Our site provides links to other sites. When you click on one of these links, you are leaving our site and entering another site that we do not control and for which we cannot be responsible. You should carefully review the privacy statements or policies on any other site that you visit because those privacy statements or policies will apply to your visit to that site and may be very different from our policy.

## Contact Us

If you have any questions or concerns about this policy or our information handling practices, you may contact us at [privacy@NYCAirporter.com](mailto:privacy@NYCAirporter.com "Email to: privacy@NYCAirporter.com"). We will attempt to respond to your questions or concerns within five (5) business days after we receive them. Alternatively you can write to us at : [feedback@NYCAirporter.com](mailto:feedback@NYCAirporter.com "Email to: feedback@NYCAirporter.com")
